

NGUYEN KHANH MINH

22/05/1981

Male

0944479057

Khanhminhpharma@gmail.com

◆ K103/7 Nguyen Du Street, Hai Chau District, Danang city.

CAREER OBJECTIVESP

Applying experiences gained during previous job on sale skills and understanding of the market to become a professional salesperson, bring more values to customers, helping companies increase sales and customer expansion, thus helping yourself get a professional working environment with reasonable and stable income.

SKILLS

Office computer, Internet

Sale

Marketing

HOBBIES

Reading

Footbal

EDUCATION ANH TRAINING

* DUY TAN UNIVERSITY

Major: University Pharmacist

Very Good

* DANANG ECONOMICS-TECHNOLOGY SCHOOL

Majors: Information Technology

Graduated with Excellent certificate



EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

* DANAPHA PHARMACEUTICAL JOINT-STOCK COMPANY

03/2005 - 02/2017

07/2013 - 07/2017

07/2000 - 07/2002

Sales Manager in the provinces of Thua Thien Hue, Da Nang, Tay Ninh, Binh Phuoc, Dak Nong.

- Jobs:

In charge of management ETC segment (Hospitals, Medical Centers, Clinics):

- Put company's products on the drug procurement list of hospitals, medical centers, make and package tender documents.
- Managing collaborators and salespeople
- · Managing and implementing the contract with the successful bidder.
- · Sales and management of customer debts.
- Capture information on market / competitors.
- Implementation of the benefits that customers are entitled under the policy of marketing, sales, promotions, customer care in areas prescribed by the company.
- Develop corporate image and maintain good relationships with clients (doctors, pharmacists, ...).

* KALBE INTERNATIONAL PTE. LTD

4/2017 - 12/2017

Medical representatives in the provinces of Da Nang

- Develop portfolio, bidding documents provided Health Insurance medicine at hospitals and health centers in regional areas.
- Recommended effective business policies.
- Sales and Customer Care, company image building and maintaining good relationships with customers.



CERTIFICATES

- TOEIC certificates 2016

- English Certificate at B level 2001

- CPE Certificate training Advanced Pharmacy skills 2011



Excellent staff at Danapha Pharmaceutical JSC company in 2012, 2013.

2012 - 2013



- Have a good health, able to work independently.
- Dynamic, enthusiastic and willing to learn .
- Have the spirit of solidarity and sociable.
- Have the spirit of high responsibility and passion for the job.
- Ability to work well under pressure.